authoroo.com 2015-06-03

# authoroo » Just another WordPress site » Privacy Statement

This Privacy Policy covers the Authoroo treatment of personal information that is recorded when you submit an article, or request an article via email. Other than the information requested in our online forms, no other information is collected from visitors to our web site.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other companies advertised, or otherwise listed, on the Authoroo web site, nor does it extend to people that Authoroo does not employ or manage.

Authoroo collects minimal personal information when you request or submit an article. The only information collected in these instances is your name, email address, IP address and the date of your request or submission.

Authoroo does not provide or guarantee author anonymity. Authors who wish to remain anonymous should either NOT complete the Author Profile in their member accounts OR complete it using a Pen Name.

Although discovering an Author’s real identity is difficult if a Pen Name is used in submitting articles, there are several ways for that information to be found if the Author Profile is completed with your real name and identity details.

If you are Authoroo Author member, your use of our service constitutes a business relationship wherein we provide a promotion service for your article(s). In exchange, Authoroo reserves the right to use the contact information collected during member registration to deliver notices regarding changes or updates to our service, to provide a free newsletter, to inform you of additions to Authoroo, or to send announcements and carefully screened offers and information on behalf of our partners or advertisers.

You may remove yourself from any or all of our mailings at anytime using the unsubscribe methods provided in those mailings. Any mailing received from our company is clearly identified and includes a valid email address and unsubscribe link which you can use to remove yourself from future mailings. Should you encounter problems in this regard, contact us here.

Spam complaints will result in membership termination.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Authoroo maintains your email address and other pertinent information in a secure database. Your contact information is never released or sold to any vendor, partner or outside agency. Authoroo, however, reserves the right to contact Authoroo members via email as deemed necessary. Such mailings will always include detailed unsubscribe information, providing members the option of removing themselves from future Authoroo mailings at any time.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Authoroo may amend this policy from time to time. If significant changes are made in the way your personal information is used, we will post a prominent announcement on our site notifying you of the change.

Your email address information is stored in a protected directory. Access is restricted to Authoroo staff.

Use advanced navigation for a better experience.   
You can quickly scroll through posts by pressing the above keyboard keys. Now press **Esc** to close this window. 

Back to Top ↑
